<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="resourceContent">
        <![CDATA[
        <big><p style="color:red;"><b>In case of an Emergency, call 9-1-1. </b></p></big>
        <p>If you require Police assistance but are not in an emergency situation where no person or property is in immediate danger, please call the <b>Toronto Police Service non-emergency number at (416) 808-2222</b>.
        </p>
        <br/>

        <big><p><b>Crime Prevention Association of Toronto</b></p></big>
        <big><a href="http://crimepreventionto.org/index-4.html">CPAT Resources</a></big>
        <br/><br/>
        <big><a href="http://crimepreventionto.org/index-2.html">Neighbourhood Watch</a></big>
        <br/><br/><br/>

        <big><p><b>Toronto Police Service</b></p></big>
        <big><a href="https://www.torontopolice.on.ca/">Toronto Police Service</a></big>
        <br/><br/>
        <big><a href="http://www.torontopolice.on.ca/crimeprevention/">Crime Prevention Tips</a></big>
        <br/><br/>
        <big><a href="https://data.torontopolice.on.ca/">Public Safety Data Portal</a></big>
        <br/><br/><br/>

        <big><p><b>Other</b></p></big>
        <big><a href="https://www.222tips.com/">Crime Stoppers</a></big>
        <br/><br/>
        <big><a href="https://crimepoint.info/crime-prevention/">CrimePoint</a></big>
        <br/><br/>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="aboutNWTO">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
        <big><b>About</b></big><br/>
        The NWTO App was designed by Heather Wang, Daniel Lee and Don Cameron and was programmed by Heather Wang and Daniel Lee.
        This App is sponsored by the Crime Prevention Association of Toronto.
        </p>

        <p>
        <big><b>Data</b></big><br/>
        The NWTO App draws data from the Toronto Police Service (“TPS”) Public Safety Data Portal database.
        These data are published by the Toronto Police Services in accordance with the Municipal Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.
        </p>

        <p>
        <big><b>Location Data</b></big><br/>
        The location data provided by the TPS is approximate.
        The database protects the privacy of individuals involved in the reported incident by adjusting the reported location of the incident to the nearest road intersection.
        The NWTO App sometimes reports a crime location as an intersection – sometimes as a street address.
        Accordingly, the crime did not occur at that address, but “near” that address – that is, within a block of that address.
        Also, due to the offset of occurrence location, the numbers reported by geographic area are approximate and may not reflect the exact number of crimes that happened within that area.
        </p>

        <p>
        <big><b>Assaults</b></big><br/>
        Most assaults are committed by people who know the victim. Therefore, the reports of assaults do not reflect the number of random assaults.
        </p>

        <p>
        <big><b>Theft Over</b></big><br/>
        “Theft Over” refers to theft of property valued over $5,000 (excluding vehicles, which are counted as “Auto Thefts”).
        </p>
        ]]>

    </string>
</resources>